fastrecharge.com 2014-04-01

# FASTRECHARGE.COM :: Privacy policy

FastRecharge is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by the Site. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Site's Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, You must discontinue using the services on this Site and terminate you registration. By using or accessing the Site, You expressly and impliedly accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

 **User Consent**

By submitting personal information in your profile, including contact details etc., you register to the site and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy. User Personal Information may be processed by the Site in the country where it was collected as well as other countries (including India). 

 **Collection and Use of Information**

The Site uses any information voluntarily given by you to enhance their experience in the network of the Site so as to make the content useful for others on the basis of their interest. Please note that you post the Content on the Site at his/her own risk. Although the Site allows setting privacy options that limit access to User pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. The Site cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, the Site cannot guarantee that User Content/ User posts on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. The Site is not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. User must understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored Your Content.

 **Confidentiality**

This Site only shares User Information with others when it has user's permission or under the types of circumstances described in this Privacy Policy. In addition, the Site may limit access to User Information to only those employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you.

The Site has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about User and his/her account information is protected by a password selected by you. The Site uses industry-standard (Secure Socket Layer) SSL encryption in certain areas of the Website to protect data transmissions. However, no site can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

 **Changes in the Privacy Policy**

If there is a change in the privacy policy, it will prominently be posted in the form of a notification on the site's homepage so that You are always aware of what information is being collected, how is it being used it, and under what circumstances, if any, it is disclosed.

If at any point the Site decides to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, it would be notified to you by way of an email.

Users will have a choice to allow/disallow the Site the use of their information in this different manner, and the Site will then use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. The Site encourages you to periodically review this page for the latest information on Site's privacy practices.
